Okay, class! Find a partner and hold hands!
"Friends Work Together!"
Wanna be my partner?
Sure!
Everyone have their partner?
Oh?
Where's your partner, Miyamura-kun?
Who wants to be Miyamura-kun's partner?
Miyamura?
Eww, no! He's weird!
"Science Lab"
We'll be doing an experiment today,
so get into groups of five.
--Can I join you guys?
--Hey, thanks.
Miyamura's left over again... He's so gloomy.
He's totally impossible to read.
Hey, someone take Miyamura.
Ugh...
"Ugh"... yeah.
Ow!
School is hard.
Honestly, it's kind of impressive
how gloomy he is all the time.
Who is?
Miyamura, duh!
Miyamura? Who's that?
What do you mean, who?
Where have you been, Hori-san?
For the next classics report,
we have to group up with the
person next to us on the roster.
What're you doing?
N-Nothing.
You just hid something, though.
Apparently we're gonna be
grouped up on the next report.
Oh. O-Okay, uh...
My name's Hori.
You should at least know the
names of the people in your class.
Sorry.
Didn't she just say she
didn't know who I was, though?
Everyone says you're all dark and gloomy.
Yeah.
That's why I talked to you.
But wow,
you're totally normal!
Hori-san's kind of weird.
"Horimiya"
Where's my name?
"That's Why It's Okay"
I can't see!
I found my name! I'm in Class 1 with you, Yuki!
Yay!
Class 1, Class 1, c'mon, Class 1...
What class're you in, Ishikawa?
Oh, I'm in Class 1.
Yes! I'm in Class 1, too!
Miyamura, I'm in your class!
Isn't that awesome?! It's the power of love!
Wait... love?
Wait, love? Because they're in the same class?
Are those two dating?
Yes! We'll be together till graduation!
What class are you in, Miyamura?
Hori-san...
Whoa, why are you tearing up?!
They're whispering about me!
C'mon, man up about it!
Knock it off, Yoshikawa.
You're gonna break his spine.
Aww.
Hey, Ishikawa, you know how
you gave me that song I wanted?
I totally deleted it by accident yesterday.
Ugh, c'mon, man.
--Yeah, my storage was full,
so I went to delete stuff and poof.
--Sometimes, I wonder.
--Yeah, my storage was full,
so I went to delete stuff and poof.
--Sometimes, I wonder.
--I thought you bought
the one with the most space.
--I did! That's why I thought I'd be safe!
--I'm in this group...
--Man, their new album is so good.
--but am I really a part of it?
--I have to wait till my older sister
finishes with the CD first though.
Now I want the new album, too.
"All About Chemical Reactions"
Okay! Go ahead and split up into
groups of four to work on your reports.
Miyamura, are you all by yourself?
Yoshikawa, gimme a pen!
You've got a million, right?
I don't have a million!
Pen bullies like you don't get a pen!
You suck.
Anyone have the packet?
Oh, I have it.
"All About Chemical Reactions"
Mmkay, Hori'll turn our outline into a draft.
Do we have enough paper?
Yeah, probably.
Miyamura, you handle the chart.
Oh, okay.
"Kyoko Hori"
"Yuki Yoshikawa"
"Izumi Miyamura"
"Toru Ishikawa"
Hori! Toru won't give me my pen back!
Because I'm still using it!
Knock it off, you two!
Friends...
Are we friends, though?
Are they cool with me being their friend?
There you are, Miyamura.
Ishikawa-kun.
I heard our next class got
switched from Math to Econ.
Shoot, did I bring that textbook today?
Really wish they wouldn't
switch things up on a dime.
Hey, man...
What do you think, Miyamura?
What?
What?! I thought you were listening to me!
Uh, hey, so...
Ishikawa-kun, what... do you think of me?
You can't ask people that with
a straight face. It's creepy as hell.
"Creepy"
You can't ask people that with
a straight face. It's creepy as hell.
"Creepy"
And I'm super annoyed about you
getting along so well with Hori.
"Annoying"
"Creepy"
And I'm super annoyed about you
getting along so well with Hori.
"Annoying"
"Creepy"
And you never say what you mean.
That's so frustrating.
"Annoying"
"Frustrating" "Creepy"
And you never say what you mean.
That's so frustrating.
"Annoying"
"Frustrating" "Creepy"
You act weird sometimes, too.
You're way too nice to people.
I always have to keep an eye on you.
And when you take off your glasses and put
your hair up, you're prettier than most girls.
It's annoying as hell.
So I'm pretty...
I hate that, too! How you get
me to say the dumbest shit!
You drive me frickin' crazy!
How is that my fault?!
You're also the only person
who calls me by my last name,
so I kinda wonder what you think of me, too.
T-Toru.
Dude!
Don't say it if you're just gonna
get all embarrassed, you idiot!
I-I just said it out loud, jeez! I just...
I... yeah.
Come to think of it, that's
the first time ever in high school
that I've called a classmate
by their first name.
You know...
You're kind of weird.
Miyamura, you're weird!
--Sorry.
--You're weird...
...but that's okay.
You're just kind of awkward.
You got that, Izumi?!
It'll be okay.
I wish I could go back
ten years and tell myself that.
Hori, listen, you gotta avoid flicking the bone!
I told you we were gonna
finish our report over lunch!
Where the heck did you wander off to?!
The roof, to affirm our friendship.
What? You're creeping me out, you two idiots.
Hey, Yoshikawa's here,
so there are three idiots!
Hey! What did you just call me?!
Hey, Ishikawa-kun. Morning.
So I watched that show you
said you liked, Ishikawa-kun.
Hey, Izu-- Miyamura, what
part did you like the most?
Let's see...
Here I thought we were
on a first-name basis now...
This guy's a total mystery.
Ishikawa-kun? Are you listening?
"Hori"
Hey, sis, you done yet?
You're heading to school already?
Yeah! Yuna-chan's waiting for me.
This early?
Sota's been getting up way
earlier now that he's in grade school...
Man, nobody's even here yet.
Can I sit here?
Ayasaki-san?
I totally thought we had a
morning assembly today. Whoops!
Yeah, same.
So Miyamura-kun's pretty hot, huh?
Huh? You think so?
Are you his girlfriend, Hori-san?
No, I'm not!
Huh, okay.
Can I have him, then?
Wait... have him?
I mean, you're not dating, right?
So you wouldn't care
if him and I got close, yeah?
Yeah, but...
Okay, Miyamura-kun's all mine!
No.
You can't have him. I'm not giving him to you.
Huh? But you said you're just friends, right?
I'm not giving you Miyamura.
I'm taking him!
No, you're not!
But Miyamura-kun's not your boyfriend!
He doesn't belong to you!
Miyamura's...
Miyamura's mine! You can't have him!
Not ever!
I'll never let you have him!
Wonder if the cafeteria's open yet.
O-Okay, bye!
I'm so stupid. Miyamura
doesn't belong to anyone.
I know I shouldn't be
surprised, but seriously...
Sota needs to stop changing in here
before he goes out to play!
Huh? He's not here again today?
He probably came home,
then went right out to play soccer.
What an energetic little rascal.
You can't do blueberries, right, Hori-san?
Ever since Sota started grade school,
we've been spending a lot
more time alone together.
That fruit tart you brought over
the other day was really good.
Whoa, really? I actually made that one.
Oh, cool! That's neat.
Sometimes, our conversations peter out.
That looked totally real!
C'mon, it's just CG. Special effects.
You're just saying that because
you're scared, right? Right?!
No, that's just the only way it
could pop out at them like that.
C'mon, Miyamura. It's just my phone.
Oh, my mom's gonna be late again.
I'm so embarrassed.
A blackout?
H-H-Hori-san! Where's your breaker box?!
It'll be back in a second. Calm down.
Calm down?!
See? It's back.
This house is definitely cursed!
What're you looking so scared for?
Okay, let's move on to disc two!
Disc two?! There are more
in this horror collection?!
"IT COULD HAPPEN TO YOU:
Real Horror Stories #49"
Disc two?! There are more
in this horror collection?!
"IT COULD HAPPEN TO YOU:
Real Horror Stories #49"
How many discs are there?!
"IT COULD HAPPEN TO YOU:
Real Horror Stories #49"
We're gonna watch the first three,
"IT COULD HAPPEN TO YOU:
Real Horror Stories #49"
then the last two after Sota gets home.
We're watching five?!
Wow, Yoshikawa-san was right.
You're double-jointed.
I'm what?
Your finger.
Oh, yeah.
Dang, Yuki, your hands are tiny!
Wait, what're you doing?
Doesn't it make your heart skip a beat
when someone grabs your hand?
I dunno.
Look at Yuki's hands! They're so tiny!
Sure, but your hands are small
compared to us guys, Hori.
I'm not comparing them to guys' hands right now.
Grab my hand and you're a dead man.
You hear that, Miyamura?
I could die if I touch Hori!
It's okay, Ishikawa-kun! My hand's open!
No thanks!
Whoa, your finger's double-jointed!
Is it just your index finger?
Yeah, it's always been like this.
Did you break it or something?
Nope, just born that way.
I wonder how the joint works.
No idea. I'd have to get an x-ray.
Your hands are so pale, Miyamura.
Is that a writer's callus, Hori-san?
Yeah.
It's so weird how your hands
are bigger than mine, Miyamura!
Huh? Isn't that normal?
I totally thought they were smaller.
I, I love you.
What?
Your hands! I love your hands,
they're--they're nice!
My hands?
Yeah! I was just thinking, "Man, I love 'em!"
Thanks. And I hold my pencil right,
so I don't have a callus like you.
H-Hey! No fair!
Well, cool.
I love yours, too.
Okay.
I love you.
Yeah, I heard you.
Okay.
I'm back!
Hey, there!
Sota! Did you wash your hands?
Not yet!
What're you doing?
Hori-san put the DVDs back in
the wrong cases, so I'm fixing it.
C'mon, time for dinner!
Wash your hands, first!
You're eating with us, right, Miyamura?
Oh, yeah, if that's okay.
Okay, then you and Sota
need to go wash your hands!
You got it. Let's go, Sota.
Okay!
So I was just talking to her,
and she said she's "never
letting me have Miyamura-kun"!
What?
I mean, I was just joking,
but she got like, actually mad!
That's 'cause you take
your jokes way too far, Remi.
Yeah, but still!
Hori-san was sooo scary.
Morning, Miyamura!
Morning.
What?! What happened to your face?!
I got into a fight and got hit in the face.
You got into a fight? With who?
Ishikawa-kun.
With Toru?!
I mean, sure, he's a big dummy dum-dum,
but I never thought he'd
get violent with a friend.
U-Uhh, Hori-san, actually--
Nope, I don't want to hear it.
I know just the kind
of guy he is now, thank you!
Morning, Ishikawa!
Whoa, holy shit!
Toru!
Hey, mornin'.
You got into a fight?
Yeah.
So you beat the crap out of each other?
No, not really...
I dodged everything 'cept that first punch.
"ashamed"
Then I beat Ishikawa-kun to a pulp...
You're kinda scary, Miyamura.
Why were you fighting?
It's none of your business, Hori.
Okay, fine. I still can't believe
you two got into an actual fight.
So, Toru, who won? You or him?
What's that look for?
Oh, nothing.
Pretty sure I lost.
Look, I know it's not happening, okay?
Okay.
Seriously, dude, listen!
I'm listening! I swear!
Hori's in love with you, Miyamura.
You mentioned that before,
but I still think you're wrong.
You're just imagining things--
I am not!
How would you react if I said I wasn't?
Are you trying to psych me out?
If Hori said, to your face,
that she loves you, what would you say?
Would you just brush it off like that?
Hori-san just sees me as a friend.
Why do you keep going back to that?
Because if I don't, you'll keep
asking me the same question.
Well, yeah, but...
Besides, it's obvious
she doesn't like me like that.
I'd like to know why you think you're right.
Well--!
I know your own feelings
probably influence your perception,
but you can't assume how
Hori-san feels without asking her.
Look!
"WHACK"
Y-You startled me, okay?!
You moron!
Moron?! You're insulting me now?
What gives, Ishikawa-kun?!
You're not gonna listen otherwise!
--The hell does that mean?!
--It means--
Shit, sorry!
That hurt.
Yo, your eyes are scary!
Miyamura! Time out, time out!
It... It was self-defense!
You beat the shit out of me!
That was uncalled for and
has nothing to do with Hori!
It was just 'cause I startled you, then?
No, I was also kind of pissed at you.
You're not supposed to admit that!
You're freakin' me out, man!
I pushed Miyamura too far. It's my fault.
I'm so sorry, Miyamura.
C'mon, go apologize to him and make up.
Wow, Miyamura said it was all his fault.
That's not what Toru said.
First they beat each other up,
now they both take the blame?
They're so weird.
I know!
Man, what were they even fighting about?
We were fighting about Hori-san.
Please don't tell anyone.
What? What is it?
It's so cool that guys can just
duke it out with each other.
Yeah, it sure is.
"Everybody Loves Somebody"